{"examName":"Exam Set for Syllabus ID [105] for Topic with ID [1] - level 0 - rank 0 - DE - DE set-2 v-2","set":2,"version":2,"SampleSet":false,"id":"0000054683-00002-00002-0","uid":0,"time":0,"starttime":0,"duration":0,"questionIndex":0,"questionTotal":90,"firstname":"","lastname":"","answerOptions":[],"examQuestions":[{"question_id":"0000000183","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [183]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000098","answer_text":"This answer with id [98] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [183]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000099","answer_text":"This answer with id [99] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [183]","correct":0},{"answer_id":"0000000101","answer_text":"This answer with id [101] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [183]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"8771a3d17acffeecde3d9a232b8b33efc70935754a04fcdaaa906f4a40cd4ec0741a07610cd5e84351dcb181335c586f05222068013b9621ea497d51cf44e0e1"},{"question_id":"0000000184","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [184]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000093","answer_text":"This answer with id [93] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [184]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000094","answer_text":"This answer with id [94] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [184]","correct":0},{"answer_id":"0000000095","answer_text":"This answer with id [95] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [184]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"5fa210a218b1c5d111695269c30ad9985e1943a6168d6a4700caaa1cc095c6463e6c76003f489917066533a67464f982e4d198142da5cbe0ce6d0ad02293ca02"},{"question_id":"0000000185","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [185]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000102","answer_text":"This answer with id [102] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [185]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000103","answer_text":"This answer with id [103] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [185]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000105","answer_text":"This answer with id [105] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [185]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"54827b57fdf144d3d05a59f8d15999e7e8cae1cf3f291fa065fd19080ac43dcf8bb359fda980c6afe805c5c73668efd16c630ba4e6ffbcf12c0d6621402a77c8"},{"question_id":"0000000186","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [186]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000108","answer_text":"This answer with id [108] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [186]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000111","answer_text":"This answer with id [111] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [186]","correct":0},{"answer_id":"0000000113","answer_text":"This answer with id [113] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [186]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"afd30fe121300cce98b9e21aca016bf4750935a8a1cc5fc9530b439da40972525c543fc5cd03b85c50cd86bf02a4ffc732019e9d1a6aa0f4966c0623e13cab29"},{"question_id":"0000000187","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [187]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000114","answer_text":"This answer with id [114] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [187]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000118","answer_text":"This answer with id [118] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [187]","correct":0},{"answer_id":"0000000119","answer_text":"This answer with id [119] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [187]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"96199908ef37e00c11a4a504f69f706e483cae39c6cfcbc5b189f2df5d26d74fa92c0112a4f4107d9c2e1abf750a235ec6bec5d191ac4253cabe691060422580"},{"question_id":"0000000188","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [188]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000121","answer_text":"This answer with id [121] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [188]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000122","answer_text":"This answer with id [122] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [188]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000124","answer_text":"This answer with id [124] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [188]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"c3a5268e8104ca037d276b789782d94436079daa2727fa31d0041e6f0623281f551f3d28e641ea977cc87d754923e2919235a7fc36876afa09edb57f4fb4ac4e"},{"question_id":"0000000189","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [189]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000128","answer_text":"This answer with id [128] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [189]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000130","answer_text":"This answer with id [130] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [189]","correct":0},{"answer_id":"0000000131","answer_text":"This answer with id [131] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [189]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"130d63e90080dff0569dcb686f17e5efe3256f220168fc53d36189b1327d055700fd3916a93ec8a6af00f955c7a26fe27a47556c0a56788a52f00451a24d637d"},{"question_id":"0000000190","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [190]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000134","answer_text":"This answer with id [134] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [190]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000135","answer_text":"This answer with id [135] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [190]","correct":0},{"answer_id":"0000000137","answer_text":"This answer with id [137] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [190]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"260bc88309391ef5de93630793a269b57a694f3d83e07629c56ca5acbb86f44a2bc400d4c9ae7a4818e8ccdab7b06da63d34e868f835eebf69b0b80612affa99"},{"question_id":"0000000191","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [191]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000138","answer_text":"This answer with id [138] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [191]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000141","answer_text":"This answer with id [141] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [191]","correct":0},{"answer_id":"0000000143","answer_text":"This answer with id [143] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [191]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"315254f61d542578bc374127930552648e6a3848a74491c9e3bde42b8957ae3e6c23d576b2e8e2b298754d731425da1512d26752407242b556e7ee0bc504c34d"},{"question_id":"0000000193","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [193]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000150","answer_text":"This answer with id [150] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [193]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000151","answer_text":"This answer with id [151] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [193]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000154","answer_text":"This answer with id [154] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [193]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"f2ed5e874024abf1cca0977871a5d943c7d6d392af89696638c0aa2098bc3f64d87deca610f29f4931ff3a0be5a0e1b6d3f79ee452708aa0dbe180f21b29ec7a"},{"question_id":"0000000194","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [194]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000156","answer_text":"This answer with id [156] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [194]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000157","answer_text":"This answer with id [157] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [194]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000159","answer_text":"This answer with id [159] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [194]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"8e2f6270b43d570264e79c4953276684dc588090113812bcc3fa150972f7110593a20562453212f6c28f6493836cae21ed52eba59634010ebd610cae58b48aab"},{"question_id":"0000000195","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [195]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000161","answer_text":"This answer with id [161] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [195]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000162","answer_text":"This answer with id [162] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [195]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000164","answer_text":"This answer with id [164] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [195]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"8d21f24b08e93a7437f9f19525408bbb8aa9f4fd410e7e3e1e9c01b04a50abd4632dce9bf55ddd1f31000626267eb99bc5a5d2aeaf3449fae58e661d05e8421b"},{"question_id":"0000000196","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [196]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000168","answer_text":"This answer with id [168] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [196]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000170","answer_text":"This answer with id [170] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [196]","correct":0},{"answer_id":"0000000269","answer_text":"This answer with id [269] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [196]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"31f1a02d7f89ee8d3c0586f93207416033e6e7db617f1ea17a35e57646eae0916027e4f6ebbd43169e73bc3fda8885a798ea3ab2872711d2651371b0da51e0b6"},{"question_id":"0000000197","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [197]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000172","answer_text":"This answer with id [172] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [197]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000173","answer_text":"This answer with id [173] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [197]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000176","answer_text":"This answer with id [176] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [197]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"2363e971578880a48e0aa893c8f3d72acf169a25b864614aa120544a6283a9808d15fafbbfa30ad306e28eb31556aa215baf20e434ce91b4145206e2d9094840"},{"question_id":"0000000198","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [198]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000180","answer_text":"This answer with id [180] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [198]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000182","answer_text":"This answer with id [182] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [198]","correct":0},{"answer_id":"0000000183","answer_text":"This answer with id [183] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [198]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"df2c7bcf051f63a75571712aba87c600bf43025e8f287f713d6eec044923775e3fd85ab636387691e156e6c84c750237ede97d43a3412a000bb40910dfa902a1"},{"question_id":"0000000199","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [199]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000185","answer_text":"This answer with id [185] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [199]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000186","answer_text":"This answer with id [186] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [199]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000187","answer_text":"This answer with id [187] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [199]","correct":1}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"d0131114e2713db21a8db58345f8eb8d654d4ed8ab26a20b59f700f4be384fd36864cda9cdee4b8d85e1010925a4a5b20b4983885833470b8c730cb21c1d4d7e"},{"question_id":"0000000204","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [204]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000215","answer_text":"This answer with id [215] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [204]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000216","answer_text":"This answer with id [216] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [204]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000217","answer_text":"This answer with id [217] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [204]","correct":1}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"9cea508a7fc35cd62340d047b3320bf06e62f513163adc4173742b0730d4a2a091eb2ef125f40c405d87ab7d3fa96473b18b84c7313defc6cf64fe84983ce1e6"},{"question_id":"0000000205","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [205]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000221","answer_text":"This answer with id [221] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [205]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000222","answer_text":"This answer with id [222] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [205]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000223","answer_text":"This answer with id [223] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [205]","correct":1}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"ebd43548d72630f2823276c6fd25874cb6771d57afb9ebf49f58cfebca2d15ca8a3a063ec0bd48416a2d48dbdd51b6460e69fbd22f66217782a4985a4ed6de23"},{"question_id":"0000000206","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [206]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000227","answer_text":"This answer with id [227] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [206]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000229","answer_text":"This answer with id [229] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [206]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000231","answer_text":"This answer with id [231] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [206]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"859ddca87106d32b619b70c4da6a6b7eedba2afea52f8879e57a70554def39e7fac67b2b6722e45a369040ae2b6f141c01f1e26593a203b5ebd6a6da34b28ed5"},{"question_id":"0000000210","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [210]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000251","answer_text":"This answer with id [251] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [210]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000254","answer_text":"This answer with id [254] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [210]","correct":0},{"answer_id":"0000000256","answer_text":"This answer with id [256] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [210]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"925cb88896808b4ef81b7967aeeaf99ccc4b4269cd4dc18785bd03c31796082b1918f024460cbea4d5dd6e09bfaddcf5b2b9589c37f9f43a5d558002d2a4fee8"},{"question_id":"0000000212","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [212]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000263","answer_text":"This answer with id [263] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [212]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000264","answer_text":"This answer with id [264] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [212]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000268","answer_text":"This answer with id [268] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [212]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"e03e37d5b89ee5e4557092539dd59b3bb10aa210ba51b0cb869ae7fbfee06941da85d7294eb8e4ebd02f883d61b961238e4e0c289315da0c47fc82b5776f45cd"},{"question_id":"0000000213","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [213]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000270","answer_text":"This answer with id [270] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [213]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000273","answer_text":"This answer with id [273] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [213]","correct":0},{"answer_id":"0000000274","answer_text":"This answer with id [274] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [213]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"e040e1641ed4e76c3ddc93f83a7ba3034e2f01a9e0ae2d0d5a583cc274b917c37958b07cd28cf55d88e3bb2ba0af46c9b86a6ad608f52124d912876b65bdaf23"},{"question_id":"0000000214","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [214]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000278","answer_text":"This answer with id [278] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [214]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000279","answer_text":"This answer with id [279] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [214]","correct":0},{"answer_id":"0000000281","answer_text":"This answer with id [281] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [214]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"83e58c70b80d1350d324332072d1826f664c62c99ac0c5bf8bdfd087eb8973e9306e9a3d931280a5019979b8c24e8080d7309cb635c80cc267e1af48270b95f2"},{"question_id":"0000000215","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [215]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000282","answer_text":"This answer with id [282] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [215]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000283","answer_text":"This answer with id [283] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [215]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000285","answer_text":"This answer with id [285] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [215]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"c9ece971b152e047527489108a02179fe129aeb125f8f054b9020c4b54153bdb8b4b61a65df09206257474a420aa3f9b95e554f1a41b495d7af180cfff4cd6f9"},{"question_id":"0000000216","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [216]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000289","answer_text":"This answer with id [289] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [216]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000291","answer_text":"This answer with id [291] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [216]","correct":0},{"answer_id":"0000000293","answer_text":"This answer with id [293] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [216]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"56b56e9ba39902158132f80539b20038dc11e91dc28b07ad4d9294cf56f43723987830a022f70a5d43e0f76f012449f7c020fba55f85e9bcc3a74a7d8dea2b14"},{"question_id":"0000000217","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [217]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000295","answer_text":"This answer with id [295] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [217]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000297","answer_text":"This answer with id [297] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [217]","correct":0},{"answer_id":"0000000298","answer_text":"This answer with id [298] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [217]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"3763a2d961d912a93a53b49534c22200ecab433c282175980493bb334e803b81e0e2b8d8e3f1e491bf716d4a82b9ab1cb7cce09061b83782a232b989cec82a45"},{"question_id":"0000000218","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [218]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000302","answer_text":"This answer with id [302] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [218]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000303","answer_text":"This answer with id [303] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [218]","correct":0},{"answer_id":"0000000304","answer_text":"This answer with id [304] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [218]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"0c033a30c3fae6fd09164a7e291f843f19cc54e41633c7c7e09ef01a441918b12a58399220ba0069573f6aff33c872fc905fa6ac2ad78734d4e5d6675c071ae5"},{"question_id":"0000000220","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [220]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000312","answer_text":"This answer with id [312] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [220]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000313","answer_text":"This answer with id [313] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [220]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000314","answer_text":"This answer with id [314] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [220]","correct":1}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"f7281fdc4d901a9d7d3eb9f06045728cb4235ccc110b7775d3156b5dbb2000e78cd5d2e862f85834bf1f4f0e7dcff09de8fb358f498dc864e040024c22772f54"},{"question_id":"0000000222","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [222]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000325","answer_text":"This answer with id [325] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [222]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000487","answer_text":"This answer with id [487] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [222]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000489","answer_text":"This answer with id [489] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [222]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"e615526e69f344e93c4ea6740229926b535406f49e62370e28a07da110e2e7a8d51fb7a5284da72b7c58c507aac8eb972a5438469a7ca8f6c22b6635caefa948"},{"question_id":"0000000223","question_text":"Is this a question with the ID [223]?","answers":[{"answer_id":"0000000333","answer_text":"This answer with id [333] is correct. It is associated to question with ID [223]","correct":1},{"answer_id":"0000000334","answer_text":"This answer with id [334] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [223]","correct":0},{"answer_id":"0000000335","answer_text":"This answer with id [335] is wrong. It is associated to question with ID [223]","correct":0}],"answersSelected":[],"answersHash":"5c68fae79fa70f2081e8fc9f9d2c19f69598cc389ac266589a5c6f555bb46062676c835be7916e959dcf864f208af227765b4d8e2f56c3af644cb797ecfdbbf5"}]}